encompass.com 2019-08-25

# Privacy Policy

____  __

**Making a purchase at Encompass.com is 100% safe**  
When we request personal information from you (such as, name, address, phone number, credit card number) it is done on our secure servers. We use industry standard technology to protect confidential information - SSL (Secured Socket Layer) - an advanced encryption technology that makes personal information unreadable as it travels over the internet.

We realize that customers are concerned about how the information they provide on-line will be used. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will use the information we collect about you to process your order and provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details regarding our Privacy Policy.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
When you place an order, we ask you to provide information to complete and fill the order by filling out and submitting an on-line form. This information includes your name, mailing address, e-mail address and credit card information. All information regarding our on-line customers is stored on a highly secured server that is not accessible through the Internet.

Encompass.com is committed to the protection of the privacy of its customers and website visitors. Currently, our website systems do not automatically capture any personal information identifiable to you, including your e-mail address, unless you specifically give it to us.

We do not sell our customer lists or customer information to third parties.

To continuously assess the value of our on-line shopping experience, we may track the way customers use our site; however, this information is analyzed only as a whole and not at the individual level. We employ Google tracking technology within the shopping cart strictly to analyze sales volume. No personal information is being recorded or used in any way.

**Children's Online Policy**  
Encompass Parts is committed to the preservation of online privacy for all of its web site visitors, including children. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Encompass.com sells products intended for purchase by adults. If you make a purchase on Encompass.com, you are representing that you are an adult. If you are a child under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using Encompass.com.

**Phone Numbers**  
In an effort to provide you with superior customer service throughout your transaction, we may require your phone number when registering or completing your sale. Having your phone number will allow us to contact you in case we need to speak to you about your order to correct or complete inaccurate information.

**Cookies**  
Encompass Supply Chain Solutions also uses 'cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a string of characters that can be written to a file on the user's hard drive when the user visits a Web site. Only the Web site that set the cookie can read it, and it can only be used as a record keeping device to store information that the site already has. It cannot, for example, be used to read other information from the user's hard drive.

Encompass Supply Chain Solutions uses cookies to track users' activity through the site in order to improve the site's architecture, to offer the user interactive features that would not be possible without them, and to recall specific information to save the user time during subsequent visits to the site. If you wish to prevent certain or all cookies from being set to your hard drive you may disable them in your browser's preferences, although your browser might then be unable to accommodate certain functionalities on Encompass.com. 

__ __
